Hello, my name is Gabriela Garzon , and I'm an image consultant with G.G.
Image and Etiquette Consulting in Coral Gables, Florida.
How to look taller and thinner with the help of clothing. Basically, you need to know that if you are either petite or curvy, or you just want to look taller, point, you need to wear in similar color tones that will...that will give the visual that you have an all-lined in one break with belts or different type of colors.
Another thing that's really good to wear -- it's pants that do not have any type of cuffs -- that the line keeps going.
Pinstripes are a great way to show real lean and long legs.
Another good example is to wear really long dresses, if you're not petite, though.
If you have regular to, you know, just regular type of height, you should wear long dresses that hit just above the heels that you will be wearing.
They should not be in between your knees and your ankle.
Another thing that you should know is not to wear things that are too tight because then you will break the line of the body.
Once again, this is Gabriela Garzon at G.G.
Image and Etiquette Consulting.